Are you new in town?
I suppose.
Another poor soul.
What brings you to the government office?
To deliver money.
Come in first.
Master, Gesang.
Clear sky, divine earth.
Old immortals, reveal the true forms.
Immortals, help me open my magic eyes.
Demons and monsters, reveal your true forms.
Those who disobey shall be captured.
A powerful demon.
Master.
Our men are ready.
Let's go.
Please wait here, everyone.
I will go in and report first.
Everyone.
I am Gu Yanqing, the Deputy Magistrate of Tangcheng.
What brings you here?
Deputy Magistrate.
We are here to deliver money.
This...
What is the meaning of this?
This is ill-gotten wealth.
Please accept it according to the procedures, Deputy Magistrate.
Return them to the people.
There are still such noble people in this world.
What a pity.
A pity?
It's easy for you to come in,
but hard to get out.
Deputy.
I know there is something strange about Ercheng.
Tell us, and we might be able to help.
Even the government office can do nothing.
How can the three of you help?
If it's about bandits or civil affairs,
I wouldn't want to interfere.
But if it's monsters causing trouble,
I can actually be of some help.
You've already run into them.
Did you promise to stay?
You must have promised to stay.
Otherwise, how could you still be alive?
The three of us killed all those monsters.
Please don't boast.
We stayed at Miaoren Bathhouse last night.
That Wen Jiuniang was a monster in disguise.
We have slain all the monsters in the building.
Please step into the inner hall to talk, Masters.
Please.
Please have a seat.
You have everything here.
Did you really kill the demon in Miaoren Tang?
See for yourself if you don't believe us.
Heaven always leaves a way out.
The Heavens have finally opened their eyes.
Are you an official from the Sitian Bureau?
No.
Although I am not a Sitian Bureau official,
I do know a thing or two about subduing demons.
What exactly happened in Ercheng?
Please tell us, County Deputy.
That was three years ago.
Three years ago, Ercheng was not as prosperous as it is today.
There were only hot springs here,
and it was a remote area.
Until that day,
when a beautiful woman came to the city,
named Ruixi.
Look at that lady. She's so beautiful.
She's so pretty.
Yeah, so attractive.
What a beautiful lady.
What is she doing in our Ercheng?
Look at that box.
It looks very heavy.
What's in it?
I don't know.
Please inform the county magistrate.
I have something to ask of him.
Greetings, Your Honor.
State your name.
I am Rongxi,
from Jiangnan.
I just arrived here,
and wish to do some business.
Ercheng has free trade.
If you wish to do business,
report to the Supervisory Bureau,
follow the legal procedures,
and you can open your shop.
Why come to the county office?
That would be true for a small business.
But what I intend to do
is something that will greatly change
Ercheng's commerce.
Naturally, I must inform the Magistrate.
What kind of business do you want to do, my lady?
Open it.
Wow.
So much silver.
Look at all this silver.
What is the meaning of this, my lady?
I want to start a money-lending business in Ercheng.
Money lending?
There are already many pawnshops in Ercheng.
How do you plan to
improve Ercheng's trade with this?
Pawnshops require jewelry and fine silk as collateral.
Poor families without jewelry or fine silk
naturally cannot borrow money.
From now on,
all merchants and commoners in Ercheng
can borrow money from me.
For foreign trade
or city construction,
I guarantee sufficient funds.
And no collateral is required.
That is so nice.
So Ruixi is a good person.
Didn't the County Deputy say
that Ruixi is a demon?
How can demons be good?
Humans can be good or evil.
Why can't there be good demons?
County Deputy, please continue.
At first,
Magistrate Shen also thought it was a good thing.
If you do this, miss,
for you,
there's no guarantee for the silver you loan out.
I trust the people of Ercheng.
But if the borrowers really can't repay the silver,
what then?
Do you really have no conditions?
No.
But there is only one catch when borrowing from me.
The interest will be slightly higher.
I don't need collateral.
It's understandable that the interest rate is a bit higher,
right, My Lord?
I will let you give it a try.
I now permit you to open a money-lending shop in Ercheng.
From today on,
any merchants or commoners in Ercheng in need
can go to you to borrow money.
This matter is of great consequence.
It concerns the livelihood and commerce of Ercheng.
Do not act recklessly.
You must abide by the law
to help keep Ercheng's trade routes open and the people prosperous.
If you hike up the interest rates and exploit the people,
don't blame me for being strict with the law.
Then I thank you on behalf of the people of Ercheng, My Lord.
Ping Jie, Qiang Haihui.